Preliminary Guide to the Africa News Service (Durham, N.C.) Leroy T. Walker Africa News Service Archive, 1952-1998 and undated (bulk 1952-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Africa: Countries (Box 24)
  - Algeria (Box 24)
    - Women, 1976-1994 (Box 27)
  - Angola (Box 27)
    - Bibliography, 1974-1994 (Box 27)
    - Culture, 1975-1994, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Diplomacy, 1970-1975, (2 folders) (Box 27)
      - Africa, 1973-1975 (Box 28)
      - Southern Africa, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
    - Economy (Box 28)
      - 1968-1994, (10 folders) (Box 28)
      - Agriculture, 1971-1993, (3 folders) (Box 28)
      - Aid, 1989-1993 (Box 28)
      - Aid, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Industry, 1970-1995, (5 folders) (Box 29)
      - Oil, 1969-1994, (3 folders) (Box 29)
      - Transport, 1970-1992, (3 folders) (Box 29)
      - Workers, 1972-1981, (4 folders) (Box 29)
    - Education, 1975-1994, (4 folders) (Box 29)
    - Foreign Relations, 1974-1975, (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 30)
      - 1976-1993, (10 folders) (Box 30)
      - Africa, 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 30)
      - Africa, 1977-1993, (3 folders) (Box 31)
      - Southern Africa (Box 31)
        - 1975-1994, (7 folders) (Box 31)
        - Zaire, 1976-1982 (Box 31)
        - Zambia, 1977-1982 (Box 31)
    - Health, 1976-1993 (Box 31)
    - Legal System, 1974-1992 (Box 31)
    - Media, 1970-1994, (3 folders) (Box 31)
    - Military, 1961-1973 (Box 31)
    - Military, 1974-1981, (10 folders) (Box 32)
    - Military (Box 33)
      - 1982-1994, (7 folders) (Box 33)
      - Mercenaries (Box 33)
        - 1974-1983 (Box 33)
        - Trial, 1976 (Box 33)
    - Politics, 1966-1975, (4 folders) (Box 33)
    - Politics, 1975-1987, (9 folders) (Box 34)
    - Politics (Box 35)
      - 1988-1994, (6 folders) (Box 35)
      - FLEC, 1974-1994 (Box 35)
      - FNLA, 1965-1992, (3 folders) (Box 35)
      - MPLA, 1960-1990, (8 folders) (Box 35)
      - Neto Death, 1979-1981 (Box 36)
      - Neto Speeches, 1975-1980 (Box 36)
      - UNITA, 1970-1992, (11 folders) (Box 36)
      - UNITA (Box 37)
        - Democratic Refketuib Tebdabat (DTR), 1992 (Box 37)
        - Kwacha News, 1988-1991 (Box 37)
        - Reference, 1974-1991 (Box 37)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 37)
    - Reference, 1976-1992 (Box 37)
    - Refugees, 1974-1994 (Box 37)
    - Religon, 1970-1994 (Box 37)
    - Society, 1989-1993 (Box 37)
    - Women, 1972-1992, (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - Youth, 1978-1991, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Benin (Box 37)
    - General, 1970-1994, (6 folders) (Box 37)
  - Botswana (Box 37)
    - Bibliography, 1980-1991 (Box 38)
    - Economy, thru 1973-1994, (5 folders) (Box 38)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 38)
      - 1970-1993 (Box 38)
      - Southern Africa, 1970-1994, (3 folders) (Box 38)
      - General, 1970-1993, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Politics (Box 38)
      - 1970-1994, (3 folders) (Box 38)
      - Seretse Khama, 1950-1952 (Box 38)
    - Reference, 1968-1980 (Box 38)
  - Burkina Faso (was Upper Volta) (Box 38)
    - General, 1973-1994, (11 folders) (Box 39)
    - Reference (Box 39)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 39)
      - Volta, 1976-1980 (Box 39)
  - Burundi (Box 39)
    - General, 1972-1994, (10 folders) (Box 39)
    - Reference, 1965-1980 (Box 40)
  - Cameroon (Box 40)
    - Economy, 1970-1993, (3 folders) (Box 40)
    - Foreign Relations, 1979-1994 (Box 40)
    - General, 1957-1994, (5 folders) (Box 40)
    - Lake Nyos Gas Leak, 1986-1987 (Box 40)
    - Politics (Box 40)
      - 1973-1994, (4 folders) (Box 40)
      - Social Democratic Front, 1992-1993 (Box 40)
  - Canary Islands (Box 40)
    - General, 1977-1979 (Box 40)
    - Canaries M.P.A.I.A.C., 1976-1978 (Box 40)
  - Cape Verde (Box 40)
    - General, 1973-1994, (3 folders) (Box 40)
    - General, 1981-1994, (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Central African Republic (Box 41)
    - General, 1970-1994, (10 folders) (Box 41)
  - Chad (Box 41)
    - Economy, 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Foreign Relations, 1972-1983, (3 folders) (Box 41)
    - Foreign Relations, 1984-1994, (4 folders) (Box 42)
    - General, 1971-1988, (3 folders) (Box 42)
    - Military, 1978-1993, (3 folders) (Box 42)
    - Politics, 1971-1979, (6 folders) (Box 42)
    - Politics (Box 43)
      - 1979-1993, (9 folders) (Box 43)
      - Claustre Affair, 1975-1978 (Box 43)
  - Comoro Islands (Box 43)
    - General, 1972-1982, (6 folders) (Box 43)
    - General, 1983-1993, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Congo (Box 44)
    - Economy, 1972-1993, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Foreign Relations, 1975-1994, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - General, 1972-1994 (Box 44)
    - Politics, 1971-1994, (4 folders) (Box 44)
  - Diego Garcia (Box 44)
    - General, 1974-1982, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Djibouti (Box 44)
    - General, 1972-1994, (7 folders) (Box 44)
  - Egypt (Box 44)
    - Bibliography, 1978-1984 (Box 45)
    - Culture & Travel, 1989-1993 (Box 45)
    - Economy (Box 45)
      - 1972-1994, (9 folders) (Box 45)
      - Reference, 1973-1976 (Box 45)
      - Suez Canal, 1974-1994 (Box 45)
      - Tourism, 1987-1994 (Box 45)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 46)
      - 1973-1994, (7 folders) (Box 46)
      - Libya, 1971-1978, (2 folders) (Box 46)
      - Mideast Conflict, 1970-1981, (7 folders) (Box 46)
      - Mideast Conflict, 1982-1994, (8 folders) (Box 47)
      - Persian Gulf, 1990 (Box 47)
      - USSR, 1972-1990 (Box 47)
    - General, 1973-1993, (7 folders) (Box 47)
    - Health, 1990-1994 (Box 48)
    - History (Ancient), 1976-1994 (Box 48)
    - Politics, 1971-1984, (12 folders) (Box 48)
    - Politics, 1985-1994, (5 folders) (Box 49)
    - Reference, 1974-1985 (Box 49)
    - Religion, 1972-1994, (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - Women, 1973-1993 (Box 49)
  - Equatorial Guinea (Box 49)
    - General, 1971-1994, (6 folders) (Box 49)
    - Reference, 1978-1983 (Box 49)
  - Eritrea (Box 49)
    - General, 1974-1984, (11 folders) (Box 50)
    - General, 1985-1994 (Box 51)
    - Reference, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Eritrea Information, 1980-1986 (Box 51)
      - Symposium on Eritrea, Jan. 79, 1979-1991 (Box 51)
      - Vanguard, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
      - Women Pamphlets, 1980-1983 (Box 51)
    - Women, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Economy,1994 (Box 51)
    - Politics, 1985-1994, (4 folders) (Box 51)
  - Ethiopia (Box 51)
    - Bibliography, 1978-1994 (Box 51)
    - Economy (Including Drought), 1970-1984, (6 folders) (Box 51)
    - Economy (Including Drought) (Box 52)
      - 1985-1994, (5 folders) (Box 52)
      - Foreign Response, 1984-1992, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - Refugees, 1984-1994, (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Foreign Relations, 1972-1981, (3 folders) (Box 52)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 53)
      - 1982-1994, (3 folders) (Box 53)
      - Northeast Africa, 1971-1994, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - General, 1979-1994, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Military, 1988-1991 (Box 53)
    - Politics, 1969-1977, (6 folders) (Box 53)
    - Politics (Box 54)
      - 1977-1994, (13 folders) (Box 54)
      - Human Rights, 1990-1994 (Box 54)
      - Oromo Liberation Front, 1992 (Box 55)
      - Peace Talks, 1988-1991 (Box 55)
      - Seilassie Obtituaries, 1975-1992 (Box 55)
      - TPLF, 1979-1990, (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Reference, 1975-1981 (Box 55)
    - Religion (Box 55)
      - 1977-1992, (2 folders) (Box 55)
      - Jews, 1983-1994, (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Gabon (Box 55)
    - Economy, 1971-1994, (4 folders) (Box 55)
    - General, 1972-1994, (4 folders) (Box 55)
    - Politics, 1973-1994, (3 folders) (Box 55)
  - Gambia (Box 55)
    - Bibliography, 1980 (Box 55)
    - Economy, 1973-1994 (Box 55)
    - Foreign Relations, 1970-1993 (Box 55)
    - General, 1970-1975 (Box 55)
    - General, 1976-1994, (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Politics--Senegambia, 1982-1993 (Box 56)
    - Refugees, 1992 (Box 56)
  - Ghana (Box 56)
    - Culture, 1973-1993 (Box 56)
    - Economy, 1961-1994, (10 folders) (Box 56)
    - Education, 1973-1993 (Box 56)
    - Foreign Relations, 1966-1994, (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - General, 1960-1994, (5 folders) (Box 57)
    - Health, 1977-1992 (Box 57)
    - Media, 1981-1994 (Box 57)
    - Politics, 1972-1981, (5 folders) (Box 57)
    - Politics (Box 58)
      - 1982-1994, (5 folders) (Box 58)
      - Human Rights, 1983-1994 (Box 58)
    - Reference, 1958-1992, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Religion, 1974-1992 (Box 58)
    - Women, 1975-1993 (Box 58)
  - Guinea Bissau (Box 58)
    - Bibliography, 1978-1980 (Box 58)
    - Economy, 1972-1994, (3 folders) (Box 58)
    - Foreign Relations, 1971-1974, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Foreign Relations, 1975-1994, (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - Health, 1973-1993 (Box 59)
    - Military, 1970-1989, (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Politics (Box 59)
      - 1973-1994, (7 folders) (Box 59)
      - Cabral Assassination, 1972-1982 (Box 59)
      - PAIGC (Box 59)
        - 1973-1981 (Box 59)
        - Actualities, 71 (Box 59)
    - Reference, 1970-1982 (Box 59)
    - Women, 1970-1980 (Box 59)
  - Guinea (Conakry) (Box 59)
    - Economy, 1976-1993 (Box 59)
    - General, 1959-1975 (Box 59)
    - General, 1976-1994, (6 folders) (Box 60)
  - Ivory Coast (Box 60)
    - Economy (Box 60)
      - 1971-1994, (4 folders) (Box 60)
      - Reference, 1959-1988 (Box 60)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 60)
      - 1972-1994 (Box 60)
      - Southern Africa, 1971-1992 (Box 60)
    - General, 1977-1994, (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Politics, 1971-1979 (Box 60)
    - Politics, 1980-1994, (12 folders) (Box 61)
    - Religion, 1988-1994 (Including the Basilicia) (Box 61)
  - Kenya (Box 61)
    - Bibliography, 1981-1991 (Box 61)
    - Culture, 1979-1993 (Box 61)
    - Economy, 1970-1982, Dec., (11 folders) (Box 61)
    - Economy (Box 62)
      - 1983-1994, (6 folders) (Box 62)
      - Agriculture, 1980-1994 (Box 62)
      - Tourism, 1972-1994, (2 folders) (Box 62)
      - Transport, 1990-1993 (Box 62)
      - Wildlife, 1972-1993 (Box 62)
    - Education, 1972-1994 (Box 62)
    - Foreign Relations, 1970-1988, (6 folders) (Box 62)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 63)
      - 1989-1994, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Africa, 1971-1994 (Box 63)
        - Somalia, 1977-1989 (Box 63)
        - Tanzania, 1980-1985 (Box 63)
        - Uganda, 1977-1989 (Box 63)
    - General, 1973-1993 (Box 63)
    - Health, 1978-1994 (Box 63)
    - History, 1981-1991 (Box 63)
    - Legal System, 1973-1992 (Box 63)
    - Media, 1973-1993 (Box 63)
    - Politics, 1969-1978, Aug., (6 folders) (Box 63)
    - Politics, 1978, Sept.-1989, (13 folders) (Box 64)
    - Politics (Box 65)
      - 1990-1993, (5 folders) (Box 65)
      - Ethnic Violence, 1992-1994 (Box 65)
      - Human Rights, 1988-1994, (3 folders) (Box 65)
      - F.O.R.D., 1992-1994 (Box 65)
    - Reference (Box 65)
      - 1964-1990 (Box 65)
      - Publications, 1971-1994 (Box 65)
    - Refugees, 1988-1994 (Box 65)
    - Religion, 1973-1994 (Box 65)
    - Society (Box 66)
      - 1974-1989 (Box 66)
      - Asians, 1970-1991 (Box 66)
      - Population, 1984-1993 (Box 66)
    - Sports, 1979-1993 (Box 66)
    - Women, 1971-1992 (Box 66)
  - Lesotho (Box 66)
    - Economy, 1970-1993, (4 folders) (Box 66)
    - Foreign Relations, 1972-1994, (4 folders) (Box 66)
    - General, 1972-1992 (Box 66)
    - Politics, 1965-1988, (7 folders) (Box 66)
    - Politics, 1989-1994, (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Reference (Box 67)
      - 1972-1989 (Box 67)
      - "Work For Justice", 1988-1995 (Box 67)
  - Liberia (Box 67)
    - Bibliography, 1980-1992 (Box 67)
    - Economy, 1972-1994, (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Education, 1976-1992 (Box 67)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 68)
      - 1974-1994, (7 folders) (Box 68)
      - West Africa, 1983-1992, (9 folders) (Box 68)
      - West Africa, 1993-1994 (Box 69)
      - Southern Africa, 1971-1985 (Box 69)
    - Health, 1978-1992 (Box 69)
    - Legal System, 1977-1991 (Box 69)
    - Media, 1975-1991 (Box 69)
    - Politics, 1971-1983, (10 folders) (Box 69)
    - Politics (Box 70)
      - 1984-1994 (Box 70)
      - National Patriotic Reconstruction, Assembly Gov't 1991-1992 (Box 70)
    - Reference, 1980-1993 (Box 70)
    - Refugees, 1990-1994 (Box 70)
    - Religion, 1979-1993 (Box 71)
  - Libya (Box 71)
    - Bibliography, 1982-1988 (Box 71)
    - Economy, 1970-1994, (6 folders) (Box 71)
    - Foreign Relations, 1970-1984, (8 folders) (Box 71)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 72)
      - 1985-1994, (4 folders) (Box 72)
      - Chad, 1971-1991, (3 folders) (Box 72)
      - North Africa-Mideast, 1970-1994, (4 folders) (Box 72)
      - Southern Africa & Africa-General, 1973-1992 (Box 72)
    - General, 1973-1992 (Box 72)
    - Politics, 1974-1983, (6 folders) (Box 72)
    - Politics, 1984-1994 (Box 73)
    - Reference (Box 73)
      - 1970-1991 (Box 73)
      - Economy, 1980-1983 (Box 73)
    - Women, 1980 (Box 73)
  - Malagasy (Madagascar) (Box 73)
    - Economy, 1980-1994, (3 folders) (Box 73)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 73)
      - 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 73)
      - Southern Africa, 1970-1990 (Box 73)
    - General, 1971-1994, (3 folders) (Box 73)
    - Politics, 1971-1994, (5 folders) (Box 73)
  - Malawi (Box 73)
    - Bibliography, 1974-1990 (Box 73)
    - Economy, 1970-1981, (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Economy, 1982-1994 (Box 74)
    - Foreign Relations, 1971-1992 (Box 74)
    - General, 1969-1994, (3 folders) (Box 74)
    - Politics (Box 74)
      - 1969-1994, (6 folders) (Box 74)
      - Chakufwa Chihana, 1992-1993 (Box 74)
      - Human Rights, 1987-1994, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Mali (Box 74)
    - Economy, 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - General, 1972-1994, (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Politics, 1960-1994, (3 folders) (Box 75)
  - Mauritania (Box 75)
    - Economy, 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 75)
      - 1972-1992 (Box 75)
      - Polisario Conflict, 1974-1984, (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - General, 1973-1991, (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - Politics (Box 75)
      - 1976-1994, (2 folders) (Box 75)
      - Human Rights, 1979-1991 (Box 75)
  - Mauritius (Box 75)
    - Economy, 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - General, 1970-1983, (3 folders) (Box 75)
    - General, 1989-1993 (Box 76)
  - Morocco (Box 76)
    - Bibliography (Box 76)
    - Economy (Box 76)
      - 1970-1994, (7 folders) (Box 76)
      - Tourism, 1979-1988 (Box 76)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 76)
      - 1972-1994, (5 folders) (Box 76)
      - Northern Africa and Spain, 1973-1984, (3 folders) (Box 76)
      - Northern Africa and Spain, 1985-1994 (Box 77)
    - General, 1973-1994, (3 folders) (Box 77)
    - Media, 1987-1994 (Box 77)
    - Politics (Box 77)
      - 1970-1993, (8 folders) (Box 77)
      - Repression, 1977-1994, (2 folders) (Box 77)
    - Reference, 1986-1991 (Box 77)
    - Religion, 1986-1994 (Box 77)
  - Mozambique (Box 77)
    - Bibliography (Box 77)
    - Culture, 1975-1994, (2 folders) (Box 78)
    - Economy (Box 78)
      - 1970-1994, (10 folders) (Box 78)
      - Agriculture, 1970-1994, (4 folders) (Box 78)
      - Aid, 1983-1993 (Box 79)
      - Cahora Bassa, 1970-1994, (3 folders) (Box 79)
      - Industry, 1970-1992, (4 folders) (Box 79)
      - Reference, 1973-1974 (Box 79)
      - Transport, 1966-1993, (4 folders) (Box 79)
    - Education, 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - Foreign Relations, 1973-1981, (7 folders) (Box 79)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 80)
      - 1982-1994, (2 folders) (Box 80)
      - South Africa, 1972-1993, (5 folders) (Box 80)
      - Southern Africa, 1972-1994, (2 folders) (Box 80)
      - Zimbabwe, 1973-1980, (6 folders) (Box 80)
    - Foreign Relations: Zimbabwe, 1980-1994 (Box 81)
    - Health, 1973-1993, (3 folders) (Box 81)
    - History, 1966-1992 (Box 81)
    - Legal System, 1972-1991 (Box 81)
    - Media, 1975-1993 (Box 81)
    - Military (Box 81)
      - 1969-1994, (9 folders) (Box 81)
      - Documents By Support Groups, 1969-1985 (Box 81)
      - Demobilization, 1993-1994 (Box 81)
    - Politics, 1970-1973 (Box 81)
    - Politics, 1974-1990 (folders 13) (Box 82)
    - Politics (Box 83)
      - 1991-1994, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - COREMO, 1973-1974 (Box 83)
      - FRELIMO (Box 83)
        - 1967-1992, (8 folders) (Box 83)
        - Documents--Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 83)
      - Machel's Death, 1986-1993 (Box 83)
      - Opposition, 1974-1993, (4 folders) (Box 83)
      - Other Nationalist Groups, Pre-Independence, 1971-1974 (Box 84)
      - Peace Talks, 1993-1994 (Box 84)
      - Portuguese Colonialism, 1971-1981 (Box 84)
      - RENAMO, 1983-1994, (3 folders) (Box 84)
    - Reference (Box 84)
      - 1963-1992, (2 folders) (Box 84)
      - Government Documents, 1975 (Box 84)
    - Refugees, 1987-1993 (Box 84)
    - Religion, 1972-1994, (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - Women, 1976-1994, (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - Youth/Children (Box 84)
      - 1977-1992 (Box 84)
      - UNEMO, 1969 (Box 84)
  - Namibia (Box 84)
    - BANTUSTANS, 1962-1980, (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - Bibliography, 1971-1991 (Box 84)
    - Culture, 1985-1994 (Box 84)
    - Diplomacy, 1966-1971 (Box 84)
    - Diplomacy, 1972-1978, (18 folders) (Box 85)
    - Diplomacy, 1978-1981, (13 folders) (Box 86)
    - Diplomacy (Box 87)
      - 1981-1988, (13 folders) (Box 87)
      - Walvis Bay, 1976-1980 (Box 87)
      - Walvis Bay, 1980-1990 (Box 88)
    - Economy (Box 88)
      - 1969-1994, (4 folders) (Box 88)
      - Foreign Investment, 1971-1993 (Box 88)
      - Land, 1990-1994 (Box 88)
      - Migrants,1990 (Box 88)
      - Mining, 1970-1993, (4 folders) (Box 88)
      - Reference, 1960-1992, (5 folders) (Box 88)
      - Trade, 1990-1994 (Box 88)
      - Walvis Bay, 1990-1994 (Box 88)
      - Workers, 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 88)
      - Workers, 1973-1993, (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - Education, 1975-1993 (Box 89)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 89)
      - 1990-1994 (Box 89)
      - Africa, 1989-1994 (Box 89)
    - Health, 1979-1994 (Box 89)
    - Legal System, 1989-1993 (Box 89)
    - Media, 1977-1990 (Box 89)
    - Military (Box 89)
      - 1970-1994, (13 folders) (Box 89)
      - "Guide To Psychological Action," 1976-1977 (Box 89)
    - Politics (Box 90)
      - 1971-1987, (12 folders) (Box 90)
      - Independence, 1988-Mar. 1989, (4 folders) (Box 90)
      - Independence (Box 91)
        - 1989, Apr.- 1993, (11 folders) (Box 91)
        - Constitution, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
        - Elections -- Ref., 1989-1990 (Box 91)
        - Foreign Response/Opinion, 1987-1989 (Box 91)
      - Other Groups, 1970-1984, (3 folders) (Box 91)
      - Repression, 1972-1977, (3 folders) (Box 91)
      - Repression, 1978-1989, (4 folders) (Box 92)
      - Students (Strikes, Boycotts), 1988 (Box 92)
      - SWAPO (Box 92)
        - 1970-1994, (13 folders) (Box 92)
        - Reference, 1980-1989 (Box 92)
        - Reference: Info & Comment, 1980-1989 (Box 93)
      - Turnhalle, 1976-1993 (Box 93)
      - White Parties, 1974-1993 (Box 93)
    - Reference (Box 93)
      - 1965-1991, (6 folders) (Box 93)
      - David Mcgloin's Thesis, undated (Box 93)
    - Refugees, 1987-1993 (Box 93)
    - Religion, 1970-1990, (9 folders) (Box 93)
    - Society, 1984-1991 (Box 94)
    - Sports, 1990-1992 (Box 94)
    - Women, 1990-1993 (Box 94)
  - Niger (Box 94)
    - Economy, 1970-1993 (Box 94)
    - General, 1972-1994, (4 folders) (Box 94)
  - Nigeria (Box 94)
    - Bibliography, 1969-1989 (Box 94)
    - Culture, 1977-1994 (Box 94)
    - Economy, 1961-1983, (8 folders) (Box 94)
    - Economy (Box 95)
      - 1984-1994, (5 folders) (Box 95)
      - Oil, 1970-1994, (6 folders) (Box 95)
    - Education, 1974-1994 (Box 95)
    - Foreign Relations, 1975-1980 (Box 95)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 96)
      - 1981-1994, (3 folders) (Box 96)
      - Africa, 1972-1994, (3 folders) (Box 96)
      - Dikko Affair, 1984-1994 (Box 96)
      - Southern Africa, 1972-1994 (Box 96)
    - General, 1981-1994, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Health, 1971-1994 (Box 96)
    - Legal System, 1985-1994 (Box 96)
    - Media, 1962-1994, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Politics, 1961-1975, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Politics, 1976-1988, (10 folders) (Box 97)
    - Politics (Box 98)
      - 1989-1995 (Box 98)
      - Human Rights, 1990-1993 (Box 98)
    - Reference (Box 98)
      - 1977-1991 (Box 98)
      - Government Documents, 1965-1977 (Box 98)
    - Religion, 1981-1994 (Box 98)
    - Society, 1981-1993 (Box 98)
    - Women, 1979-1994 (Box 98)
  - Reunion (Box 98)
    - General, 1976-1991, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - Rwanda (Box 98)
    - Economy, 1970-1994 (Box 99)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 99)
      - 1977-1994 (Box 99)
      - With African Countries, 1976-1994 (Box 99)
    - General, 1992-1995 (Box 99)
    - History/Ethnic Background, 1978-1994 (Box 99)
    - Politics, 1979-1994, (6 folders) (Box 99)
    - Refugees, 1973-1994 (Box 99)
    - Society, 1983-1994 (Box 99)
    - Wildlife, 1975-1994 (Box 99)
    - Reference, 1990-1994 (Box 99)
  - Sao Tome And Principe (Box 99)
    - General, 1974-1994 (Box 99)
  - Senegal (Box 99)
    - Economy, 1976-1981, (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - Economy, 1982-1994 (Box 100)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 100)
      - 1973-1994 (Box 100)
      - Mauritania, 1989-1992 (Box 100)
    - General, 1979-1993 (Box 100)
    - Politics (Box 100)
      - 1972-1994, (5 folders) (Box 100)
      - Human Rights, 1984-1994 (Box 100)
  - Seychelles (Box 100)
    - General, 1972-1982, (7 folders) (Box 100)
    - General, 1983-1994 (Box 101)
  - Sierra Leone (Box 101)
    - Economy, 1970-1994, (2 folders) (Box 101)
    - Foreign Relations, 1977-1994 (Box 101)
    - General, 1975-1994, (2 folders) (Box 101)
    - Politics, 1971-1994, (3 folders) (Box 101)
    - Reference, 1961-1984 (Box 101)
  - Somalia (Box 101)
    - Economy, 1975-1992, (6 folders) (Box 101)
    - Economy, 1992-1994, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 102)
      - thru 1977, 1978-1994, (4 folders) (Box 102)
      - Northeast Africa, thru 1977, 1978-, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - General, thru 1980, 1981-1994, (2 folders) (Box 102)
    - Health (Box 102)
    - Politics,, thru 1976, 1977-1990, (7 folders) (Box 102)
    - Politics (Box 103)
      - 1991-1993, (3 folders) (Box 103)
      - Peace Process (Box 103)
      - Peace Talks, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 103)
      - Somali National Movement (Box 103)
      - United Somali Congress (Box 103)
    - Refugees (Box 103)
    - Religion (Box 103)
  - South Africa (Box 103)
    - Bantustans (Box 104)
      - General, 1970-1994, (8 folders) (Box 104)
      - General Pamphlets (Box 104)
      - Bophuthatswana: General, 1970-1993, (5 folders) (Box 104)
    - Bantustans (Box 105)
      - Bophuthatswana, 1994 (Box 105)
      - Ciskei, 1972-1993, (6 folders) (Box 105)
      - Gazankulu (Box 105)
      - Kangwane (Box 105)
      - Kwandabele (Box 105)
      - Kwazulu (Box 105)
        - Economy (Box 105)
        - General, 1970-1993, (6 folders) (Box 105)
        - Clarion Call (Box 105)
      - Lebowa (Box 106)
      - Qwa Qwa (Box 106)
      - Transkei (Box 106)
        - Economic, 1967-1982, (4 folders) (Box 106)
        - General, 1970-1993, (9 folders) (Box 106)
        - General Pamphlets (Box 106)
      - Venda, 1978-1993, (3 folders) (Box 106)
    - Bibliography, pre-1983 (Box 106)
    - Bibliography, 1983-1990, (3 folders) (Box 107)
    - Culture (Box 107)
      - thru 1989, (11 folders) (Box 107)
      - Censorship, thru 1987, (5 folders) (Box 107)
      - Cinema (Theatre), 1989 (Box 107)
      - Literature, 1989 (Box 107)
      - Music/Dance, 1989 (Box 107)
      - Music, Black Mambazo (Box 107)
    - Economy, thru 1968 (Box 107)
    - Economy, 1969-1978 (Box 108)
    - Economy (Box 109)
      - 1980-1993, (7 folders) (Box 109)
      - Agriculture, 1980-1993, (3 folders) (Box 109)
      - Banking (Box 109)
        - thru 1983, 1984- (Box 109)
        - Banking Reference (Box 109)
          - Nedbank Guide (Box 109)
          - South Africa Reserve Bank Quarterly Annual (Box 110)
          - Standard Bank (Box 110)
      - Black Business (Box 110)
      - Budget (Box 110)
      - Bureau For Economic Research (Box 110)